Introduction
Chapter 1 What Makes People Different from Animals
Chapter 2 The Search for Meaning in Ancient Myths and Religions
Chapter 3 The Unexpected Arrival of Christianity
Chapter 4 The Difference Between Christianity and Other Faiths
Chapter 5 The Strangeness and Power of the Christian Story
Chapter 6 The Shaping of Civilization: Christianity’s Quiet Revolution
Chapter 7 The Challenge of Christendom: Faith in Power
Chapter 8 The Modern World: Doubt, Disenchantment, and the Search for Wonder
Chapter 9 The Everlasting Man: Humanity’s Unending Quest
Chapter 10 The Invitation: Living the Story Today
Conclusion